翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
In project 0, you're going to not just create objects, but also arrays of objects.
在项目0中，你不仅要创建对象，还要创建对象数组
And this can be slightly confusing to novices.
这可能会让新手有点困惑
So what I want to do is just talk about this one case.
所以我要谈谈这个例子
Now, I'm assuming you've already done homework 0.
我假设你们已经做了作业0
So in homework 0, you learn how arrays work.
在作业0中，你会学习到数组是如何工作的
And I'm not going to talk about it in any of these videos
视频中不说了
because it's one of those things that's almost a little too boring to talk about.
因为没必要讲
And it's just a little more interesting if you have some exercise to push your way through.
最好多练习练习
So if you haven't done homework 0 yet,
如果你还没有做作业0
pause this video, go check it out.
暂停视频去做吧
It's kind of fun.
挺好玩的
And then watch the rest.
然后再来看
So the basic picture here is that if you want to create an array of objects as opposed to, say, an array of integers,
如果你想创建对象数组，而不是整数数组
you'll use new in two different ways.
需要通过两种方式使用 new
First, you're going to use the new keyword to create the actual array like this.
第一种这样创建
And at this point, there's no dogs created.
这时还没有创建狗
You can think of it as, like, you construct to dog houses that are currently empty.
可以想象成创建了空的狗窝
And it's only later that you'll say, OK, in dog house 0, put a tiny dog,
然后再狗窝0放一只小狗
and in dog house 1, put a medium sized dog so that after this code runs,
在狗窝1放一只中等狗，运行代码后
you end up with here, these two doghouses.
会得到这些，有两个狗窝
They're both full.
而且它们都满了
And I can ask, hey dog, the one in dog house 0, make a sound.
我可以这样说：“狗窝0里的那条狗，叫两声”
And it will go, "yipyipyip!"
然后她就会叫： yipyipyip
So just be aware there's two different situations here going on with new--
请注意这两种使用 new 的方式
one's for the array, and one is for each individual dog.
一种用于创建数组，一种用于创建每只狗
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）